styloko.com 2016-03-23

# Privacy policy | Styloko.com

STYLOKO’s approach to privacy

The website or app that is linked to this privacy policy is operated by Styloko Limited ("we" or "us"). 

We appreciate your interest in our website (our "_site_") or our app (our "_app_"). Privacy protection is very important to us and we are committed to protecting you and respecting your privacy. This privacy policy sets out information about how we collect, store, process, transfer, share and use data that identifies or is associated with you (hereinafter "_personal information_"). 

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, Styloko Limited is the data controller of personal information we hold about you. 

You should also be aware that we use cookies to store and access information whilst providing access to our site or our app. You can find out more about our use of cookies in our cookie policy. 

Personal INFORMATION we COLLECT about you AND HOW WE USE IT

We collect personal information about you when you voluntarily submit information directly to us, our site or our app. This can include information you provide to us when you open an account, complete a form on our site or app, correspond with us, subscribe to our mailing lists, newsletters or other forms of marketing communications, respond to a survey, enter a promotion or use some other feature of our website or app. 

We also collect personal information from you indirectly such as information about the pages you look at on our site or our app or the device you use to view our site or connect to our app with. 

The list below sets out the categories of personal information we collect about you and how we use that information. 

Contact details: We collect contact information such as your name and the email address associated with your account. We will use your contact details so that we can communicate with you directly about the services we provide and about queries, issues or concerns you or other users have. 

Comments and opinions: When you contact us directly, e.g. by email, phone, post or bycompleting an online form we will record your comments and opinions. We will alsorecord comments and opinions you express when you respond to surveys, enter competitions or take part in promotions we run. We will use your comments and opinions to address your queries, issues and concerns and improve our service. We will also use comments and opinions you express when responding to surveys, entering competitions or taking part in other promotions to help us determine services that may be of interest to you and to send you marketing communications in accordance with your marketing preferences. 

Website and app login details: Where you create an account with us we will hold your user name and password details so that we can keep your account secure. Where you are provided with the option to log-in using a social network, for example using Facebook, we will not be provided with your password or other account login details for those accounts. We will not post to your social network or to your friends, followers or contacts without your consent 

Your preferences: We hold information about the preferences you set for notifications, marketing communications and how our site is displayed or what content is displayed to you through our app. We will use your preference settings for the purpose of providing notifications, sending marketing communications and displaying our site in accordance with your choices. 

Information about how you use and connect to our site or our app: We collect information about how you use our site or our app such as the pages you view on our site or our app, the time you access our site or our app and how long you use it for, the website from where you came to our site or our app or go to after leaving our site or our app and any selections and choices you make when using our site or our app. 

We also collect information about the computer, tablet, smartphone or other electronic device you use to connect to our site or our app. This information can include details about the type of device, unique device identifying numbers, operating system, browsers and applications connected to our site or our app through the device, your Internet service provider or mobile network, and your IP address. 

The information we collect about how you use or connect to our site is associated with your device. It will also be associated with you as a named individual when you log into a registered account you have with us. 

We use information about how you use and connect to our site and our app to present our site or our app to you on your device and to determine services that may be of interest to you for marketing purposes. 

Information about your location: Other than information you choose to provide to us, we do not collect information about your precise location. Your device's IP address may help us determine an approximate location. We may use an approximate location to ensure content on our site is relevant to the area, city, state or country you are using your device in. We will not use your exact location without your consent. Where necessary we will seek your consent before using information about your exact location. 

Information provided by other users: Sometimes, other visitors to our site or users of our app provide information that is associated with you. We will use personal information about you that is contained in private messages sent to us by other users to respond to any query, issue or concern they raise. Where users of our site or our app want to invite you to use our site, our app or to share information with you about our services we will use personal information that they provide about you to assist them in doing this; we will only do this though where they indicate that you have provided your consent for them to communicate with you in this way. 

Information about fraudulent or criminal activity relating to your account: We will use information about fraudulent or criminal activity relating to your use of our site or our app for the purposes of detecting and preventing fraud or crime. 

All personal information: We will use all the personal information we collect to monitor and improve our site, our app and our procedures and processes. We also use the personal information we collect to help us develop new services. Our use of your personal information in this way will not result in information that was not previously publicly available being made public on our site or through our app. 

At various places on our site or our app you may be requested to enter certain personal information. Personal information that must be provided in order to use the requested services will be indicated at the time of collection. Other personal information that you are not required to provide in order to receive our services may be voluntarily given and you are free to decide not to give such personal information. 

We may anonymise and aggregate any of the information we collect (so that it does not directly identify you). We may use anonymised information for purposes that include testing our IT systems, research, data analysis, improving our site and developing new services and features. 

Information we share with third parties

We may share your personal information with the following parties: 

Companies in the same group of companies as us: our subsidiaries (i.e. any organisation we own or control) or our holding company or ultimate holding company (i.e. any organisation that owns or controls us) and any subsidiaries they own. These companies will only use your personal information in the same way as we can under this privacy policy. 

Service providers and advisors: third parties who provide a service to us. For example, third party service providers help support our IT infrastructure, develop analytical information for us about our services and provide professional services such as legal and accountancy services. These third parties will only be allowed to use your personal information in accordance with our instructions and will be required to keep your information secure. 

Purchasers of our business: personal information may be disclosed or transferred to buyers or perspective buyers of our business or any of our assets as part of any such sale. 

Law enforcement, regulators and other parties for legal reasons: third parties who we are under a legal obligation to disclose your personal information to or to whom we need to disclose your personal information to protect our rights, property or safety or to protect the rights, property or safety of others. We may also disclose personal information to third parties to help detect and investigate illegal activities and breaches of any agreement we have with you. 

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to anyone else except as set out above. We may provide third parties with aggregate statistical information and analytics about users of our site or our app but we will make sure no one can be identified from this information before we disclose it. 

Marketing and Advertising

By signing up to our service you recognise that we will contact you with information about our services and the latest fashion trends we think are of interest to you. Most messages we send will be by email. If you are using our app we may also send you push notifications. If you do not want to receive marketing messages from us, you will be able to tell us by selecting certain boxes on the forms when we first collect your contact details. 

We send several emails a week to our subscribers and you can adjust the frequency of or the number of emails you receive by changing your preferences in the settings section of your account on our website. 

You can also opt out of receiving messages by following the instructions outlined below. 

Email – click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our marketing emails. If you have an online account with us you may also be able to opt-out of marketing emails through your account settings. 

App push notifications – you can change your push notification preferences at any time in the account settings for the app. 

Where you have given us permission to do so, we may share your contact details with selected third parties so that they can provide you with information about services that they believe may be of interest to you. We will only do this if you have given us your express consent to do so. 

If you decide you no longer want us to share your contact details with selected third parties for marketing purposes, you can let us know by contacting us using our contact details at the end of this privacy policy. If you have an online account with us you may also be able to tell us not to share your contact details with third parties through your account settings. 

ONLINE ADVERTISING

We, or our advertising partners, may show advertisements to you on our site, our app, in messages we send to you or on other websites or apps. To do this we, or our advertising partners, collect information about how you use or connect to our site, our app or the types of other web pages, social media services, content and ads you, or others who are using the device you connect to our site or app with, interact with, visit or view. The information collected might also include the IP address of the device you connect to our site or our app. 

We, or our advertising partners, use the information that is collected to make sure the adverts you see either on our site, our app, our messages, other parties’ websites and apps (where our partners have advertising space) are more relevant to you. 

Typically cookies and similar technologies are used to provide this type of advertising. You can find out more about cookies and how to manage their use by reading our cookie policy. 

Storing and transferring your personal information

Cookies and Local Storage: we may store information (which may include personal information) locally on your device using cookies and other browser and application storage methods. For further information please see our cookie policy. 

Security: we implement appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect your personal information against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, change, or damage. 

International Transfers of your Personal Information: the personal information we collect may be transferred to and stored in countries outside of the jurisdiction you are in. Some of these jurisdictions offer differing levels of protection in respect of personal information and may, in certain instances, be less protective than the jurisdiction you are typically resident in. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with applicable law and this privacy policy. 

Accessing and correcting your personal information

You have the following rights in relation to your personal information: (i) the right to be informed about how your personal information is being used; (ii) the right to access the personal information we hold about you; and (iii) the right to request the correction of inaccurate personal data we hold about you and to request the blocking or deletion of your personal information where the processing does not comply with local data protection laws. To exercise any of the above rights, or if you have any questions relating to your rights, please contact us by using the details set out in the "Contacting us" section below. 

If there is personal information which you think we hold, please contact us using the contact details set out in the “Contacting us” section below. Please provide as much information as you can about the personal information you are looking for and we will be happy to try and help you find it. 

Links to third party sites

Our site contains links to third party websites of our partner networks, advertisers, partner merchants, news publications, retailers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check the individual policies before you submit any information to those websites. 

Changes to this policy

We may update this privacy policy from time to time and so you should review this policy periodically. When we change this privacy policy in a material way, we will update the "last modified" date at the top of this privacy policy. Changes to this privacy policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

Notice to you

If we need to provide you with information about something, whether for legal, marketing or other business related purposes, we will select what we believe is the best way to get in contact with you. We will usually do this through email or by placing a notice on our site. The fact that we may send notices to you will not stop you from being able to opt out of certain types of contact as described in this privacy policy. 

Contacting us

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcome and should be addressed to: 

Styloko Limited,   
21a Noel Street,   
London W1F 8GR,   
England. 

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 31.04.15
